<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Filip Mazurek</title>
    <link>https://filipmazurek.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://filipmazurek.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2019</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>https://filipmazurek.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://filipmazurek.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://filipmazurek.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://filipmazurek.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a recent graduate from Duke University with a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science. I have previously worked at &lt;a href=&#34;appian.com&#34;&gt;Appian&lt;/a&gt;, a software company, both as a software engineer and a user experience designer. After a year of work in industry, I have decided to pursue a PhD in Computer Science. I am especially interested in the quantum computing software stack, and plan to do research on quantum computing compilation, simulation, debugging, and formal verification methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My research experience includes a summer as a research engineering technician with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/index.htm&#34;&gt;NIOSH&lt;/a&gt;, a division of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cdc.gov/&#34;&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;. My research involved determining the most appropriate machine learning model, performing parameter selection, and implementing my findings as a computational model for classification of rat breathing data. Some rats had silicosis, a lung disease, and served as a representative model for human breathing. The results could be used to better classify human breathing data to help diagnose people who may have silicosis. My work was a rat-applicable extension of the article &lt;em&gt;Classification of voluntary cough airflow patterns for prediction of abnormal spirometry&lt;/em&gt;, found &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4860154/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
