<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Filip Mazurek</title>
    <link>http://www.github.io.filipmazurek/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://www.github.io.filipmazurek/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2021</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>http://www.github.io.filipmazurek/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>http://www.github.io.filipmazurek/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.github.io.filipmazurek/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.github.io.filipmazurek/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a second-year graduate student in Electrical and Computer Engineering at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.https://ece.duke.edu/.edu/&#34;&gt;Duke University&lt;/a&gt; advised by &lt;a href=&#34;https://ece.duke.edu/faculty/kenneth-brown&#34;&gt;Professor Ken Brown&lt;/a&gt;. My broad area of research is Quanutm Computing, and my main focus is working on support software for ion trap quantum computers. I am busy contributing to &lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/duke-artiq/dax&#34;&gt;Duke ARTIQ Extensions&lt;/a&gt; (DAX), an open-source project from Duke University focused on adding traditional software abstractions on top of &lt;a href=&#34;https://m-labs.hk/experiment-control/artiq/&#34;&gt;ARTIQ&lt;/a&gt;, a leading control system for quantum information experiments. The goal of the project is to provide a framework that enables the development of modular and transparently layered software for quantum control systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I aim to expand DAX further, such as by adding realistic simulation of errors characterized by our actual quantum systems at Duke University. There already exist plans for a middle-level language called DAX.program that sits between higher-level languages such as Qiskit and DAX. My other research interests include strategies for compilation from higher-level languages such as Qiskit to DAX.program as well as optimization strategies for compiling DAX.program to DAX and ARTIQ, and the corresponding system pulses that come with it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
